You guys, welcome back.
Welcome back. I hope you have done the hands-on.
You have followed all the steps.
You, you are understanding of the development lifecycle,
the development process, the testing, the communication,
communication with data analysts, communication
with cloud engineers, and all of
that is getting into your system here,
and you're able to make sense of how a typical project
goes through different steps.
Okay? Now, when we ran the job from curated
to the aggregated, you know, we,
we used five workers over there.
It took about 11 minutes only, right?
Do we need so many workers?
Do we need to finish in 11 minutes?
That's the question you gotta ask,
because whatever you, you use in the cloud,
you'll be charged for that.
Even in the real world. You gotta be thinking from the
company's financial health perspective as well, in the sense
you don't wanna necessarily spend money.
It just really no real need.
If it is OnPrem, you don't,
you wouldn't really worry about all of these things,
but when it comes to cloud,
you gotta think about the cost as well.
So we will talk about
the cost optimization part about this job later.
Okay, we'll get to that part later.
But before we go to the next video, I want to write down
in your own words,
before you see others comments in your own words,
what you've learned so far.
Okay? Lemme just read that.
Alright, do that now before we go to the next video.